Jared Harms

Rockford, MN 612-393-5577 harms.jared@outlook.com

Goal-oriented Web Developer brings strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design packages to develop custom-crafted, customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of user experience, usability and speed. Lends detailed knowledge of SEO to increase visibility.

Work Experience

NASM Certified Personal Trainer

08/2019 to Present

Fitspace, LLC.

Wayzata, MN

Personal trainer responsible for maintaining safety and well-being of members and guests, designing fitness programs to meet the needs of 30+ individuals on a weekly basis, monitoring and tracking progress of all clients goals and needs.

Cavalry Scout

10/2012 to 10/2018 United States Army Duluth, MN

The job of a Cavalry Scout is to operate as one of the first personnel in an area.

Cavalry Scouts gather information on the enemy by dismounted and/or mounted reconnaissance patrols. Cavalry Scouts engage the enemy with anti-armor weapons and scout vehicles in the field, track and report enemy movement and activities, and will direct the employment of various weapon systems onto the enemy.

Their specialized skills enable them to assist with observation and listening posts, perform and help with navigation, and help secure and transport ammunition. The Cavalry Scout leads, serves, or assists as a member of a scout crew, squad, section, platoon, or troop, in reconnaissance, security, and other combat operations.

Skills

HTML, CSS, JS, React, MySQL, Node, Express - 1 year

Education

University of Minnesota

Other
Web Development
Minneapolis, MN
06/2020 to Present

Fond du Lac Tribal & Community College

Associate
Registered Nursing
Cloquet, MN 55720
08/2014 to 05/2017